http://www.livernoismotorsports.com/privacy

Year
2021202020192018201720162015201420132012201120102009200820072006200520042003200220012000199919981997199619951994199319921991
×
ShopAPPAREL CAM PHASER LOCKOUTS, LIMITERS & KITS COLD AIR INTAKES COMPUTER & TUNING
COMPUTER & TUNING
Livernois Motorsports & Engineering continues to expand the world of tuning possibilities with our MyCalibrator tuner. Whether it comes to performance tunes, towing tunes, or fuel efficiency tunes, we are a leader in first to market production. World record breaking performance packed into one, easy to use, device. Some features include:
Custom tuning from Livernois Motorsports
Dyno proven air/fuel adjustments
Considerable HP and TQ gains
Compatible with most performance packages
Transmissions modifications with reduced torque management
Modified shift points/firmness
Enhanced throttle response
Revised rev limiter
Shop all Engines
ENGINE COMPONENTS EXHAUST FASTENERS FORCED INDUCTION FORD PERFORMANCE FORD WHIPPLE 2019 FUEL DELIVERY FUEL PUMPS NEW PRODUCTS OILING
OILING
Form GT500 pumps to EcoBoost Upper Block Supports Livernois Motorsports Powerstorm oiling components are here to have you covered.
Billet Oil Pump Gears
Oil Pumps
Drainback
Windage Trays
Catch Cans
Shop more oiling parts
5.0L BILLET OIL PUMP GEARS
MUSTANG ECOBOOST BALANCE SHAFT DELETE KIT
6.2L BILLET OIL PUMP GEARS
GT500 BILLET GEARED OIL PUMP W/ PICK UP
Shop all Oiling
PERFORMANCE PACKAGES
PERFORMANCE PACKAGES
Livernois Motorsports Installed Performance Packages are the full package, giving unmatched performance for late model Ford, GM, and Chrysler vehicles. They feature many different stage options, utilizing many of the Livernois Motorsports products.
Choose the package that is optimal for your desired power gains and we can install it in no time!
Naturally Aspirated
Forced Induction
Nitrous Oxide
Shop More Packages
2014+ GM LT1 TRUCK LEVEL 1 PERFORMANCE PACKAGE
2010-14 6.2L RAPTOR LEVEL 2 PACK
2015+ 5.0 MUSTANG GT STAGE 1 PERFORMANCE PACK
Shop all Packages
PULLEYS SUSPENSION & CHASSIS THUNDERSTORM REBATE VALVETRAIN
VALVETRAIN
Livernois valvetrain components are made in the USA and include dyno tune proven cam profiles, valve spring kits, push rods, rocker arm braces, displacement on demand eliminator kits, cam phaser lock outs and cam phaser limiter kits. All designed and engineered by Livernois Motorsports for late model perfromance trucks, cars and SUV's
Cams
Displacement on Demand kits
Valve Springs
Components
Shop More Valvetrain Components
DELUXE CAM PHASER NOISE REPAIR KIT
LS DISPLACEMENT ON DEMAND KIT
HEMI ROCKER BAR SYSTEM
6.2L RAPTOR CAM SET & VALVETRAIN UPGRADE KIT
Shop More Components
WHEELS & TIRES Cars For Sale2014 BIW CJ-style roller with other components INSTRUCTIONS & DOWNLOADSTUNER INSTRUCTIONS MYCALIBRATOR TOUCH INSTRUCTIONS PART INSTALLATION INSTRUCTIONS SOFTWARE DOWNLOADS Vehicle ServicesInstallation Services Vehicle Transport Services Dyno Services Tuning ServicesEngine ServicesEngine Build Services Machine Shop Services Cylinder Head Services MediaVideos Press Releases Social Media AboutAbout Livernois Motorsports Terms and Conditions Privacy Policy Warranty Return Policy COVID-19 updates Contacts & CareersCareers In-House Sales Manager In-House Sales Representative
Privacy Policy
At Livernois Motorsports, we take your privacy seriously. This statement describes the privacy policy for the entire Web site (all of info@livernoismotorsports.com), including what information we capture and how we use it.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
Livernois Motorsports captures information from its visitors in two different ways: directly when you submit to us and indirectly through our website server technology. Livernois Motorsports never collects or maintains information at our website from those we actually know are under 18.
LOG FILES
Our site collects traffic information from visitors to be used for statistical analysis and Web site improvement. When you access our site, we collect information about your visit in a log file on the server. Log file information may include, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not try to track you or to identify you individually, but we do review this information to understand overall trends and to determine what kinds of content are popular and useful to our visitors.
We may also use tracking and analysis software and to identify and analyze patterns of browsing by our visitors. We use this information to understand which parts of the site seem to be interesting, whether any aspects of the site seem to be confusing or overlooked, and how well our marketing activities are working.
USE OF COOKIES
Cookies are small files of information that Web sites can store on your computer's hard drive. The Livernois Motorsports site assigns a unique number-letter combination that is used only when you are on our site. This number-letter combination is used to identify and analyze patterns of browsing by our visitors.
EMAIL SENT TO US
Throughout our site, we have email addresses posted to encourage our users to contact us directly. If a user submits an email to us, we respond to the email directly to answer questions or comments. We do not sell or otherwise disclose email addresses to 3rd parties.
LINKS AND INFORMATION GATHERED BY OTHERS
Our site contains links to other sites. Livernois Motorsports does not operate any of these linked sites, cannot control what information such sites gather or what such sites do with the information, and is therefore not responsible for the activities of the operators of such sites. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by Livernois Motorsports.
CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our homepage, and/or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
However, if we plan to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify such users by email if, and to the extent that, such users have provided their email addresses to us. If you do not reply to such an email, or we receive a reply of "undeliverable" or a similar message from your last known email address, in either case after a reasonable time, we will use the information in the different manner. We may collect personally identifiable information and use such information if we are required to do so by law or if we deem it advisable in the course of assisting law enforcement activities or protecting our Web site(s) and other information.
CONTACTING LIVERNOIS MOTORSPORTS:
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or need to contact us, please use the following contact information:
Livernois Motorsports 2500 South Gulley Road Dearborn Heights, MI 48125 info@livernoismotorsports.com (313)-561-5500
"fast cache""site_page_cache inactive""cacheStatus:1""Page Not Cached""site_page_cache inactive""cacheStatus:1""Page Not Cached"
